<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Nic Prothero&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Nic Prothero&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:25:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project One, Step Two</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/project1step2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:25:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/project1step2/</guid>
      <description>Personal desire to support local agriculture becomes political due to the government importing produce from other countries for cheaper costs and a demand for year round produce.
Object Photos Texture Photos Creative Commons Photos &amp;ldquo;Honey Bee on Saw Palmetto Fruit&amp;rdquo; by bob in swamp is licensed under CC BY 2.0.
&amp;ldquo;Sorbus aucuparia fruit&amp;rdquo; by Ervins Strauhmanis is licensed under CC BY 2.0.
&amp;ldquo;Fresh Food&amp;rdquo; by Sonny Side Up! is licensed under CC BY 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project One, Step One</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/project1step1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:17:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/project1step1/</guid>
      <description>Desires and Aversions Desire to Eat Local Food
Personal desire to support local agriculture becomes political due to the government importing produce from other countries for cheaper costs and a demand for year round produce. Desire to Follow Passions
Personal and cultural desire to follow passions as a career becomes political due to many careers involving passions do not pay livable wages. Aversion to Eat Processed Food
Personal and cultural aversion to not consume processed foods clash with political as large companies are able to mass produce at cheaper and faster rates than fresh whole foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger King&#39;s Design Rebrand</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 14:23:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicP-Blog/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>After almost two entire decades, Burger King&amp;rsquo;s rebrand is a refreshing update to the old outdated look. Design wise the new campaign features a new color palette, a custom typeface, and modern yet retro illustrations. These are seen in the new packaging, digital promos, and even the uniforms.
It was quite hard for me to decide what my favorite art piece is. I decided on picking one of my favorite graphic design rebrand campaigns instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
