<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nic&#39;s Art Blog</title>
    <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nic&#39;s Art Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:53:52 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Four - Space and Place</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:53:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project4/</guid>
      <description>About the Project / Derive Notes This project uses Google Maps Street View in order to collect screenshots at a given location. These screenshots are then put into Photoshop&amp;rsquo;s auto photomerge feature in order to combine all of the images into one image.
My first attempt I digitally wandered around Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Shibuya ward. My reasoning behind selecting this location was because it is near the school where my parents met, and it is a familar location as I have visited before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Three - Monument and Sensation</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:53:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project3/</guid>
      <description>Project Statement This project is a digital rotoscope animation created in Adobe Photoshop. My project&amp;rsquo;s goal was to discuss monuments that are celebrated even though one was absent for the sensation that created them. My focus was specifically on the many monumental events and dates in ones life that are celebrated although one was not present for the sensation that provides reason for celebration. The example I decided to focus on in this project is one’s own birth and the celebration of a birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Two - Dis/Embodiment</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 13:49:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project2/</guid>
      <description>Project Statement This project is a digital portrait created in Adobe Photoshop. It was first created using collage and then digitally painted over in order to stylize and create a cohesive composition. The image&amp;rsquo;s goal was to focus on how one&amp;rsquo;s own perspective changes during times where they feel detached from their own body. These are times that are accompanied by a feeling of dissociation, mental fog, and a perception that people and things around you feel unreal or distant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project One - Tropisms</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 16:10:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1/</guid>
      <description>Project Statement This project is a digital work created to help bring to light the harm that comes with imported agriculture. The photos were collected at locally grown farmer&amp;rsquo;s markets, at typical grocery stores, and from creativecommons.org. Once the images were collected they were then digitally cut out, edited, and intentionally positioned in order to create the composition. Using these techniques, the piece highlights the increasing dangers and issues that come with the importation of international produce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project One, Step Two</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1step2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:25:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1step2/</guid>
      <description>Personal desire to support local agriculture becomes political due to the government importing produce from other countries for cheaper costs and a demand for year round produce.
Object Photos Texture Photos Creative Commons Photos &amp;ldquo;Honey Bee on Saw Palmetto Fruit&amp;rdquo; by bob in swamp is licensed under CC BY 2.0.
&amp;ldquo;Sorbus aucuparia fruit&amp;rdquo; by Ervins Strauhmanis is licensed under CC BY 2.0.
&amp;ldquo;Fresh Food&amp;rdquo; by Sonny Side Up! is licensed under CC BY 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project One, Step One</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1step1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:17:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/project1step1/</guid>
      <description>Desires and Aversions Desire to Eat Local Food
Personal desire to support local agriculture becomes political due to the government importing produce from other countries for cheaper costs and a demand for year round produce. Desire to Follow Passions
Personal and cultural desire to follow passions as a career becomes political due to many careers involving passions do not pay livable wages. Aversion to Eat Processed Food
Personal and cultural aversion to not consume processed foods clash with political as large companies are able to mass produce at cheaper and faster rates than fresh whole foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger King&#39;s Design Rebrand</title>
      <link>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 14:23:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolasprothero.github.io/NicolasProthero-ArtBlog/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>After almost two entire decades, Burger King&amp;rsquo;s rebrand is a refreshing update to the old outdated look. Design wise the new campaign features a new color palette, a custom typeface, and modern yet retro illustrations. These are seen in the new packaging, digital promos, and even the uniforms.
It was quite hard for me to decide what my favorite art piece is. I decided on picking one of my favorite graphic design rebrand campaigns instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
